William Brown McKinley Papers
William Brown McKinley Papers
1906-1920
McKinley, William Brown, 1856-1926.
30.0 linear ft.
Papers of the American legislator. McKinley was the Republican U.S. Representative(1905-1913; 1915-1920) and Senator (1920-1926) from Illinois. Collection includes correspondence, financial records, pamphlets, petitions, photographs, press releases, scrapbooks, and speeches, mostly relating to McKinley's roll as director of William H. Taft's renomination campaign prior to the Presidential election of 1912.
149161
Biographical History
William Brown McKinley, businessman and congressman, was born in Petersburg, Illinois, September 5, 1856, the son of George and Hannah (Finley) McKinley. After attending local public schools, he enrolled at the University of Illinois, Urbana, for two years. In 1881 he married Kate Frisbee of Chicago.
McKinley began a business career in the family firm of J.B. & W.B. McKinley. The company originally specialized in private banking and mortgages, then expanded into public finance and the construction of municipal utilities. In the city of his residence, Champaign, Illinois, McKinley built and controlled the trolley car lines and water, gas and electric utilities. He continued to acquire urban utilities and interurban lines across the state, eventually becoming president of both the Western Railways & Light System and the Illinois Traction Company.
After the turn of the century, McKinley served three years as a trustee of the University of Illinois, then, almost fifty, he embarked on a twenty-year career in politics. As a Republican, he was elected representative of the 19th Illinois district in the 59th, 60th, 61st, and 62nd Congresses (19051913). His unsuccessful candidacy in 1912, the year he directed President William Howard Taft's renomination campaign, was followed by three more terms in the House of Representatives (1915-1921).
McKinley left the House of Representatives for the Senate in 1920. He died on December 7, 1926, months short of completing his first term in the Senate and weeks after the disappointment of losing a renomination for a second term.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The William Brown McKinley Papers are organized into six groups: correspondence, political records, legislative documents, petitions, printed material, and scrapbooks. The larger part of the papers fall within the decade 1908-1918. One of the congressman's major assignments was the organization of the 1912 Republican Presidential Convention in Chicago in support of incumbent William Howard Taft. Most of the collection focuses on the political contest between Taft and Theodore Roosevelt for the Republican party nomination, but correspondence and election records concentrating on other campaign years are present, as well as McKinley's correspondence relating to international affairs, such as the proposed Pan-American Congress of 1906; the national issues debated in Washington, such as the tariff, the trusts and judicial reform; and the special concerns of politics in McKinley's Illinois constituency.
Among subjects of potential research value are the position of the Negro in the Republican Party, the relation of Congressman McKinley to the business community, and an abundance of contemporary comment, both crank and sophisticated, about the election issues of 1912 and the contrasting personalities of William Howard Taft and Theodore Roosevelt.
Correspondence (Boxes 1-51) consists of more than 28,000 letters, most of which were sent to McKinley and his staff in 1912 when McKinley directed the National Taft for President Bureau. Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence are attached to the incoming correspondence from supporters and opponents of the. Taft candidacy. The "Miscellaneous" folders included with some states contain anonymous, unidentified, fragmentary, group and form correspondence; and the "Miscellaneous, United States" folder in Box 51 contains the same type of materials which cannot be identified with any particular state.
Much of the correspondence appears to have been dictated by McKinley's personal secretary, John C. Eversman, as well as by Henry Casson, William Hayward and Leroy T. Vernon, all officers of the Republican National Committee and its organs in the convention, the National Taft Bureau and the Subcommittee on Arrangements. Party correspondence addressed to President Taft at the White House was often referred to McKinley for answer by the Presidential Secretary, Charles D. Hilles. After McKinley succeeded in managing the renomination of Taft at the Chicago convention, Hilles took charge of the national campaign against Roosevelt and Woodrow Wilson. There is one letter signed by President Taft which covers enclosures advocating legal reforms.
Other notable correspondents include Charles Ballinger; Charles G. Dawes, president of the Central Trust Company of Illinois, associate of McKinley, and a financier who gained prominence after World War I for his plan to cope with reparations payments; Henry A. DuPont of Delaware; and Henry L. Stim5on, Secretary of War in Taft's cabinet. Within the correspondence of several states will be found letters from governors, congressmen, civil servants, political organizers, businessmen, and voters of every opinion about the issues and personalities in the election of 1912.
Political Records (Boxes 52-56) are subdivided into national campaign records, state campaign records, financial records, speeches and position papers, press releases, and memorabilia.
National campaign records (Box 52) contain historical references from conventions antedating the convention of 1912, a few memoranda on strategy, an unbound packet of electoral statistics for all states in 1918, party organizational charts, and a scrapbook of form letters, broadsides, press releases, pamphlets and serial publications issued by the National Taft Bureau in 1912. Among the miscellaneous campaign records is a confidential packet of instructions to doormen, bandmasters, police operatives, "yell captains", and other McKinley functionaries inside convention hall. Rosters of Republican National Committee members and minutes of the Republican National Congressional Committee (Box 53) cover the period 1908-1916.
State campaign records (Box 54) are divided by state (35) and include formal assessments of political conditions on the eve of the 1912 convention, as well as copies of Republican state committee resolutions, lists of party officers, delegates and workers, memoranda on state organization, reports on local issues, and materials referring to the campaign strategy of the opposition.
Financial records (Boxes 54-55) include bills and receipts for the following expenses listed here in descending order of cost: printing, engraving, and campaign novelties; telephone, telegraph and messenger service; office and hotel rent; freight charges; decorations and military bands; office supplies. Also included in this section are expense accounts, bank deposits, drafts, statements and cancelled checks. The bills were accumulated between the years 1907 and 1916, and the larger part fall within the six-months preceding the Chicago convention of 1912. "Studies and reports" consist of lists of campaign contributors, periodic statements of receipts and disbursements of the Republican National Committee, and analyses of campaign expenditures between 1912-1917.
Speeches, position papers and press releases about President Taft and Theodore Roosevelt are located in Box 56. Memorabilia include a brochure of the Taft inauguration, itineraries, two photographs of Taft, the family genealogy, a Taft banner, a campaign ribbon and assorted campaign buttons.
Legislative documents (Box 57) contain a small group of bills and acts in draft and printed form.
Petitions (Box 57) are dated 1910 and concern boiler inspection legislation and the parcels post.
Printed materials (Box 57) consist of broadsides, government publications, magazines, separates, clippings and pamphlets about Taft, his opponents, and a range of political issues between 1906 and 1920. All titles are given in the shelf list.
There are two Scrapbooks of clippings (Boxes 58-59) taken from Chicago newspapers of June, 1912.
Arrangement of the Collection
Correspondence is arranged first according to state or territory of origin in alphabetical sequence, and within each state or territory in alphabetical sequence by name of correspondent. A small group of correspondence originating from outside the United States follows and is arranged alphabetically by country of origin. Legislative documents and petitions are in chronological order. Printed material is arranged alphabetically by type and within that in chronological order.
Subject and Genre Headings
Politics, government and public administration; McKinley, William Brown, 1856-1926 -- Archives.; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930.; Campaign management.; Political campaigns -- United States.; Legislators -- United States.; Politicians -- United States.; Presidents -- United States -- Election, 1912.; Republican National Committee (U.S.); Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States -- Politics and government -- 1901-1953.; Broadsides (notices); Correspondence.; Financial records.; Memorandums.; Pamphlets.; Petitions.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches (documents); Legislators.; Politicians.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Purchase, ca. 1963.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Alabama
    - A-W (Box 1)
  - Alaska (Box 1)
  - Arizona
    - C-W (Box 1)
  - Arkansas
    - A-W (Box 1)
  - California
    - A-L (Box 2)
    - M-Z (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Colorado
    - A-W (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Connecticut
    - A-W (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Delaware
    - B-W (Box 3)
  - Florida
    - A-Z (Box 3)
  - Georgia
    - A-Y (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Hawaii
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box 5)
  - Idaho
    - A-W (Box 5)
  - Illinois
    - A-C (Box 6)
    - Chapman, R. N. (Box 6)
    - Checkley, William N. (Box 6)
    - Clark, C. N. (Box 6)
    - Cline, C. A. (Box 6)
    - D (Box 7)
    - Dawes, Charles G. (Box 7)
    - Deneen, Charles S. (Box 7)
    - E (Box 7)
    - Eversman (miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - F (Box 7)
    - Farmer, Walter M. (Box 7)
    - G (Box 7)
    - Gregory, Charles A. (Box 7)
    - Grier, T.A. (Box 7)
    - H (Box 8)
    - Harry, M. L. (Box 8)
    - Hayward, W. M. (Box 8)
    - Hook, C. O. (Box 8)
    - I, J (Box 8)
    - James, Edmund Janes (Box 8)
    - K (Box 8)
    - L-Le (Box 8)
    - Lemon, Frank K. (Box 8)
    - Li-Ly (Box 8)
    - M (Box 9)
    - McKinley (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - McMillan, H. M. (Box 9)
    - N (Box 9)
    - O-P (Box 10)
    - Power, S. A. (Box 10)
    - Q-Ry (Box 10)
    - Rankin, A. C. (Box 10)
    - Riley, Ozias (Box 10)
    - S-Sl (Box 10)
    - Sm-Sw (Box 11)
    - Sherman, Lawrence Y. (Box 11)
    - Steele, W. A. (Box 11)
    - Torbet, L. K. (Box 11)
    - U (Box 11)
    - W (Box 12)
    - Weir, Joseph C. (Box 12)
    - Y-Z (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Indiana
    - A-Y (Box 13)
  - Iowa
    - A-H (Box 14)
    - Hunter, Edward H. (Box 14)
    - I-W (Box 14)
    - Young, Lafayette (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - Kansas
    - A-L (Box 15)
    - M-Y (Box 16)
  - Kentucky
    - A-W (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Louisiana
    - A-Y (Box 18)
  - Maine
    - A-P (Box 19)
    - Parkhurst, Frederic H. (Box 19)
    - R-W (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
  - Maryland
    - A-W (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
  - Massachusetts
    - A-W (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 19)
  - Michigan
    - A-D (Box 20)
    - Diekma, Gerrit J. (Box 20)
    - E-W (Box 20)
    - Young, H. Olin (Box 20)
  - Minnesota
    - A-J (Box 21)
    - Johnson, Marcus (Box 21)
    - K-Z (Box 21)
  - Mississippi
    - A-W (Box 21)
  - Missouri
    - A-K (Box 22)
    - L-St (Box 23)
    - Stifel, Otto F. (Box 23)
    - Su-Z (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
  - Montana
    - B-W (Box 24)
  - Nebraska
    - A-C (Box 24)
    - Currie, Frank M. (Box 24)
    - D-Z (Box 24)
  - Nevada
    - B-W (Box 25)
  - New Hampshire
    - A-W (Box 25)
  - New Jersey
    - A-L (Box 26)
    - M-Y (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - New Mexico
    - A-W (Box 28)
  - New York
    - A-Bes (Box 29)
    - Bennett, William S. (Box 29)
    - Bi-Bro (Box 29)
    - Brewster, William B. (Box 29)
    - Brogan, William G. (Box 29)
    - Browning, William J. (Box 29)
    - Bru-C (Box 29)
    - D-K (Box 30)
    - L-Y (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
  - North Carolina
    - A-Y (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - North Dakota
    - A-W (Box 32)
  - Ohio
    - A-B (Box 33)
    - Brown, M. R. (Box 33)
    - Brown, Theodore F. (Box 33)
    - Butler, Joseph G. (Box 33)
    - C-F (Box 33)
    - G-L (Box 34)
    - Laylin, Lewis (Box 34)
    - M-Y (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
  - Oklahoma
    - A-Z (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - Oregon
    - A-W (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - Pennsylvania
    - A-D (Box 37)
    - Dunlap Printing (Box 37)
    - E-K (Box 37)
    - L-P (Box 38)
    - Penrose, Boies (Box 38)
    - R-Z (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38)
  - Philippine Islands
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box 38)
  - Puerto Rico
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box 38)
  - Rhode Island
    - B-W (Box 39)
  - South Carolina
    - A-Y (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 39)
  - South Dakota
    - A-W (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
  - Tennessee
    - A-W (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
  - Texas
    - A-H (Box 41)
    - Hunt, P. B. (Box 41)
    - I-K (Box 41)
    - Keating, Joseph B. (Box 41)
    - L (Box 41)
    - M (Box 42)
    - MacGregor, H. F. (Box 42)
    - N-Z (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 42)
  - Utah
    - A-Y (Box 43)
  - Vermont
    - A-W (Box 43)
  - Virginia
    - A-Z (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 43)
  - Washington
    - A-P (Box 44)
    - Perkins, S. A. (Box 44)
    - R-W (Box 44)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 44)
  - Washington, D.C.
    - A-By (Box 45)
    - Browning, William J. (Box 45)
    - C (Box 45)
    - Cannon, Joseph G. (Box 45)
    - Curtis, Francis (Box 45)
    - D (Box 45)
    - E-H (Box 46)
    - Hilles, Charles (Box 46)
    - J-L (Box 47)
    - Loeb, William, Jr. (Box 47)
    - M (Box 47)
    - McKinley (miscellaneous) (Box 47)
    - N (Box 47)
    - Nagle, Charles (Box 47)
    - O-R (Box 47)
    - S (Box 48)
    - Shipp, Thomas R. (Box 48)
    - Stimson, Henry L. (Box 48)
    - T (Box 48)
    - Taft, William Howard (Box 48)
    - U-Y (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 48)
  - West Virginia
    - A-H (Box 49)
    - Harrison, J. Forsyth (Box 49)
    - J (Box 49)
    - K-Z (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Wisconsin
    - A-Z (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 51)
  - Wyoming
    - A-W (Box 51)
  - United States, general
    - Miscellaneous (Box 51)
  - Foreign
    - Austria (Box 51)
    - Canada (Box 51)
    - Cuba (Box 51)
    - France (Box 51)
    - Turkey (Box 51)
- Political records
  - Campaign records, national
    - Convention precedents, quotations and memoranda, 1856-1912 (Box 52)
    - Electoral statistics, 1918 (Box 52)
    - Mailing lists and organizational charts, 1903-1918 (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous convention records, 1912 (Box 52)
    - National Taft Bureau "Record Book", Mar 1912-Jun 1912; bound volume (Box 52)
      Includes form letters, broadsides, Taft Truths, Apr 23, 1912-May 31, 1912, Taft Truths, Mar 11, 1912-Jun 1, 1912, National Taft Bureau press releases, political pamphlets, clippings
    - Republican National Committee lists, 1908-1912 (Box 53)
    - Republican National Congressional Committee minutes, 1908-1916 (Box 53)
    - National Republican Congressional Committee, "Executive Committee Minutes", 1914-1915; bound volume (Box 53)
  - Campaign records, state, 1912
    - Arkansas (Box 54)
    - California (Box 54)
    - Connecticut (Box 54)
    - Delaware (Box 54)
    - Illinois (Box 54)
    - Indiana (Box 54)
    - Iowa (Box 54)
    - Kansas (Box 54)
    - Kentucky (Box 54)
    - Louisiana (Box 54)
    - Maine (Box 54)
    - Maryland (Box 54)
    - Massachusetts (Box 54)
    - Michigan (Box 54)
    - Minnesota (Box 54)
    - Missouri (Box 54)
    - Montana (Box 54)
    - Nebraska (Box 54)
    - New Jersey (Box 54)
    - New York (Box 54)
    - North Carolina (Box 54)
    - Ohio (Box 54)
    - Oklahoma (Box 54)
    - Oregon (Box 54)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 54)
    - South Carolina (Box 54)
    - South Dakota (Box 54)
    - Tennessee (Box 54)
    - Texas (Box 54)
    - Vermont (Box 54)
    - Virginia (Box 54)
    - Washington (Box 54)
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 54)
    - West Virginia (Box 54)
    - Wisconsin (Box 54)
  - Financial records
    - Bills and receipts
      - 1907-1910, 4 folders (Box 54)
      - 1912, Feb, Mar (Box 54)
      - 1912, Apr-Oct (Box 55)
      - 1912 Miscellaneous (Box 55)
      - 1913-1916, 4 folders (Box 55)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 55)
    - Studies and reports, Republican National Committee, 1912-1917 (Box 55)
  - Speeches and position papers
    - Taft, 1912 (Box 56)
    - Roosevelt, 1912 (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 56)
  - Press releases
    - Taft headquarters, 1912 (Box 56)
    - Roosevelt headquarters, 1912 (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 56)
  - Memorabilia
    - Brochure, Taft-Sherman inauguration, 1909 (Box 56)
    - Calling cards (Box 56)
    - Cartoons (Box 56)
    - Invitations (Box 56)
    - Itineraries (Box 56)
    - Photographs (Box 56)
    - Taft genealogy (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous, includes campaign buttons (Box 56)
- Legislative documents
  - 1907-1912 (Box 57)
- Petitions
  - 1910 (Box 57)
- Printed material
  - Broadsides
    - Miscellaneous (Box 57)
  - Government publications
    - War Department, Special Orders No. 266, Nov 9, 1906 (Box 57)
    - Congressional Record, 19 May 1908; 15 Apr 1910,; 10 Mar 1911 (Box 57)
    - Senate Document No. 44: "Absorption of the Tennessee Coal and Iron Company", 1911 (Box 57)
    - Hearings on House Resolution No. 314 regarding restraint of trade, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Taft, William Howard, "The Judiciary and Progress," An Address, Toledo, Ohio, 8 Mar 1912 (Box 57)
    - Senate Document No. 604, relating to the proposed prosecution of the International Harvester Company, 24 Apr 1912 (Box 57)
    - "Campaign Contributions and Publicity Acts", 1914 (Box 57)
  - Magazines, 1903-1918 (Box 57)
    - Outlook, C, No. 9, Mar 2, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Pearson's Magazine, XXVII, No. 5, May 1912 (Box 57)
    - National City Bank of New York, Bulletin, Oct 1917 (Box 57)
    - National Security League Bulletin, I, No. 1, Feb 1913 (Box 57)
  - Magazine separates
    - Murphy, W. R., "The Personification of a Square Deal," The Pioneer, XI, No. 12, Dec 30, 1907 (Box 57)
    - "Uncle Joe Cannon Hits Back at 'Success'," Printers' Ink, Mar 10, 1909 (Box 57)
    - Foote, Allen Ripley, "Federal Interference with State and Local Taxation," Ohio Journal of Commerce, Dec 16, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Leupp, Francis E., "President Taft's Own View," Ou tlook, Dec 2, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Welliver, Judson C., "Catching Up with Roosevelt," Munsey's Magazine, Mar 1912 (Box 57)
    - "Notes and Comments on the Reciprocity Bill," Paper Makers Journal, XI, No. 5, Apr 1912 (Box 57)
    - Kennaday, Paul, "Industrial Relations," Labor World, Mar 12, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Turner, George Kibbe and Arthur Wallace Dunn, "The Forces Behind Taft," McClure's Magazine, XXXIX, No. 1, May 1912 (Box 57)
    - Durand, Elliott, "Law vs. Politics," The Hamiltonian, XVIII, No. 2, Aug 1917 (Box 57)
    - "Taft Denounces Lynching", undated (Box 57)
    - "Three Presidents and the Chamber of Commerce of the United States," The Nation's Business, Jan 1918 (Box 57)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - 1908-1920 (Box 57)
  - Political pamphlets
    - Bryan, William Jennings, "Government Ownership of the Railroads", ca. 1908 (Box 57)
    - The Roosevelt League of New York, "Theodore Roosevelt and William Howard Taft: What Each Has Done.. .", ca. 1912 (Box 57)
    - "Hon. Joseph G. Cannon: His Five Years' Service as Speaker of the House", ca. 1912 (Box 57)
    - Dampman, John B., "Vote Getting: The Effective, Economical and Successful Way", ca. 1912 (Box 57)
    - "Endorsed by the President" (Box 57)
    - "Hepburn: The Friend of Labor" (Box 57)
    - "Tariff on Zinc Ore" (Box 57)
    - "Who Makes the Illinois Farmer and Farmer's Call?" (Box 57)
    - "Mrs. Seward A. Simmons.. ." (Box 57)
    - "O. H. Waddle's Declaration" (Box 57)
    - "Third Term Danger Signals" (Box 57)
    - "xxx Favors Taft" (Box 57)
    - "Square Deal Due Taft" (Box 57)
    - Stuart, T. B., "The Recall of Judges" (Box 57)
    - "Views of the Minority" (tariff) (Box 57)
    - Karger, Gus J., "Two Years of President Taft" (Box 57)
    - "Three Years of Taft: An Index" (Box 57)
    - Beath, Robert B. and others, "Open Letter to the Veterans of the Civil War" (Box 57)
    - "Do You Know Mr. Roosevelt's Exact Position?" (Box 57)
    - "Roosevelt's Broadside" (Box 57)
    - "Odezwa Prezydenta Roosevelta" (Box 57)
    - Roosevelt Progressive Republican League,"... Circumstances Attending the Movement from LaFollette to Roosevelt"; "Wherein Taft Has Failed"; "Why Women Should Vote for Roosevelt" (Box 57)
    - Feeney, James L., speech, Oct 5, 1908 (Box 57)
    - "Why Turn Down Taft?" (Box 57)
    - "Addresses Delivered by...William Howard Taft...Touching the Negro Problem", ca. 1909 (Box 57)
    - "Full Credit to Taft" (Box 57)
    - Strong, Daniel Bissel, "The Philosophy of the Trust Movement," Part II, ca. 1911 (Box 57)
    - Longworth, Nicholas, speeches in favor of the Payne Tariff Law, 1910 (Box 57)
    - Lippitt, Henry F., speech on the Woolen and Cotton Tariff, Oct 18, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Foote, Allen Ripley, "Importance of a Correct Cost Statement", ca. 1911 (Box 57)
    - "War Veterans", ca. 1911 (Box 57)
    - "Wm. H. Taft for President," Texas, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Tawney, James A., Address before the Taft Club of Minneapolis, Minnesota, Feb 9, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Stafford, Wendell Phillips, "The New Despotism," address before the New York County Lawyers Association, Feb 17, 1912 (Box 57)
    - "President Taft as a True Friend of the Colored Man", April 1912 (Box 57)
    - Jackson, Orville E., "An Open Letter to Republicans of Idaho", Apr 10, 1912 (Box 57)
    - "Contested Election Case of Aaron P. Prileau against George S. Legare," contestant's brief, Apr 18, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Taft, William Howard, address at Boston, Mass., Apr 25, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Perkins, George W., An open letter to William B. McKinley, New York, Apr 29, 1912 (Box 57)
    - Austin, Richard W., Remarks on the Underwood Tariff Law and the American Sugar Industry, May 9, 1914 (Box 57)
    - "Capt. H. Z. Osborne: Republican Nominee for Congress", Aug 25, 1914 (Box 57)
    - "Special Election for Congressman," Martinsburg, W. Va., Apr 29, 1916 (Box 57)
- Scrapbooks
  - Clippings
    - Republican presidential news stories taken from Chicago morning papers, Jun 1912
      - Volume I (Box 58)
      - Volume II (Box 59)